Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Organizations PE.036
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- I, 1872-2011; 11 Linear Feet in 9 record cartons, 2 manuscript boxes, and 4 oversize shared boxes
  - Industrial Relations Counselors, Inc., 1966-2001 (Box 41)
  - Industrial Relations Research Association, 1954-1980 (Box 41)
  - Industrial Republic Labor Party (Timberville, VA), 1979 (Box 41)
  - Industrial Research Group (New York, NY), undated (Box 41)
  - Industrial Union League/ Party (U.S.), 1932- (Box 41)
  - Industrial Union of Direct Actionists, 1907 (Box 41)
  - Indy Media, undated (Box 41, Box 125, Folder 19)
  - Infant Formula Action Coalition (San Francisco, CA), undated (Box 41)
  - Ingen Krig Mod Irak, 2002- (Box 41)
  - Ingersoll Forum (New York, NY), 1933 (Box 41)
  - Inmates Liberation Front (New York, NY), 1971 (Box 41)
  - Innergalatic Psychic Police (New York, NY), 1973 (Box 41)
  - Insane Dialectical Posse, 2003 (Box 125, Folder 20)
  - Inside Books Project (Austin, TX), undated (Box 41)
  - Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility, 1987 (Box 125, Folder 22)
  - Institute for Advanced Education (New York, NY), 1933-1934 (Box 41)
  - Institute for American Democracy, 1968, undated (Box 41)
  - Institute for Anarchist Studies, 1996- (Box 41)
  - Institute for Defense and Disarmament Studies, 1989 (Box 41)
  - Institute for Democratic Education, undated (Box 41)
  - Institute for Democratic Socialism (New York, NY), 1977- (Box 41)
  - Institute for Democratic Studies (New York, NY), 2000-2003 (Box 41)
    Materials in this file are related to reproductive rights.
  - Institute for Education and Research on Women and Work (Cornell University), 1978 (Box 41)
  - Institute for Food and Development Policy (Oakland, CA), 1972-1983 (Box 41)
  - Institute for Freedom in the Church, 1965- (Box 41)
  - Institute for Independent Social Journalism, Inc. (New York, NY), 1967- (Box 41)
  - Institute for Labor Education and Research (New York, NY), 1981 (Box 41)
  - Institute for Media Analysis (Harvard University, Cambridge, MA), 1988-1989 (Box 41)
  - Institute for New Communications, 1974, undated (Box 41)
  - Institute for Policy Studies (Washington, DC), 1975-1982 (Box 41)
  - Institute for Propoganda Analysis, 1938-1939 (Box 41)
  - Institute for Rational Urban Mobilizing (IRUM): Auto-Free New York, 2007- (Box 41)
  - Institute for Social Ecology (Plainfield, VT), 2000- (Box 41)
  - Institute for the Study of Nonviolence (Palo Alto, CA), 1972- (Box 41)
  - Institute for the Study of Labor and Economic Crisis (San Francisco, CA), 1979 (Box 41)
  - Institute for the Study of the USSR (Munich, Germany), undated (Box 41)
  - Institute for Workers' Control (Nottingham, England), 1970- (Box 41)
  - Institute of Black Political Studies, undated (Box 41)
  - Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations (University of Michigan, Wayne State University), 1980- (Box 41)
  - Institute of Working Class History (Chicago, IL), undated (Box 41)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations I, 1944-1957 (Box 41)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations II, 1942-1957 (Box 41)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations III, 1942-1957 (Box 41)
  - Institute of the Black World, 1970- (Box 41)
  - Institute of World Economics (Washington, DC), 1942- (Box 41)
  - Instituto Di Studi Sul Capitalismo, undated (Box 41)
  - Instituto Piemontese Antonia Gramsci, 1998- (Box 41)
  - Insurrectional Antitheocratic International, undated (Box 41)
  - Integrated Circuit, 1986- (Box 41)
  - Inter-American Association for Democracy and Freedom, 1950-1965 (Box 41)
  - Inter-American Federation for Democracy in Greece, 1969 (Box 41, Box 125, Folder 21)
  - Inter-American Regional Organization of Workers (ORIT), 1955-1964 (Box 41)
  - Inter-Block Council for Peace, 1968-1969 (Box 41)
  - Intercampus Network Against the Draft, undated (Box 41)
  - Inter-Citizens Committee (Birmingham, AL), 1965 (Box 41)
  - Intercollegiate Co-operative Society, 1920 (Box 41)
  - Intercollegiate Liberal Conference, 1930 (Box 41)
  - Intercollegiate Peace Association, 1911-1915 (Box 41)
  - Intercollegiate School of Individualists I, 1953- (Box 42)
  - Intercollegiate School of Individualists II, 1953- (Box 42)
  - Inter-democracy Federal Unionists, circa 1939 (Box 42)
  - Inter-Hemispheric Education Resource Center, 1986-1991, undated (Box 42)
  - International Action Center, 1999, undated (Box 42)
  - International African Service Bureau (London, U.K.), 1938- (Box 42)
  - International ANSWER Coalition (Act Now to Stop War and End Racism), 2000-2005 (Box 42, Box 122, Folder 3)
  - International Anarchist Group of Detroit, undated (Box 42)
  - International Anarchist Relation Committee of America (New York, NY), 1931-1932 (Box 42)
  - International Archive Team (London, U.K.), 1975- (Box 42)
  - International Arts and Sciences Press (New York, NY), 1958-1959 (Box 42)
  - International Association of Democratic Lawyers (Brussels, Belgium), 1956-1959 (Box 42)
  - International Association of Labour History Associations I, 1999- (Box 42)
  - International Association of Labour History Associations II, 1999- (Box 42)
  - International Association of Labour History Institutions I, 1997- (Box 42)
  - International Association of Labour History Institutions II, 1999- (Box 42)
  - International Association of Labour Museums, 2001- (Box 42)
  - International Auxilliary Co., 1919- (Box 42)
  - International Black Workers' Conference, 1971 (Box Shared Tamiment 187, Folder 9)
  - International Bolshevik Tendency, 1988- (Box 42)
  - International Brigade Association (London, U.K.), 1943 (Box 42)
  - International Brigade Wounded and Dependants' Aid Committee (London, U.K.), 1938 (Box 42)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1986 (Box 42)
  - International Campaign for Tibet, 2003 (Box 125, Folder 23)
  - International Network of San Patricios, 1994 (Box 125, Folder 25)
  - International Catholic Truth Society (Brooklyn, NY), 1934-1938 (Box 42)
  - International Caucus of Labor Committees, 1973-1984 (Box 42)
  - International Class War Prisoners Aid (London, U.K.), undated (Box 42)
  - International Commission for the Assistance of Child Refugees in Spain (Paris, France), undated (Box 42)
  - International Committee Against Racism, 1973-1981 (Box 42, Box 125, Folder 24)
  - International Committee Against Racism, 1981- (Box 42)
  - International Committee for the Defense of African Workers, undated (Box 42)
  - International Committee for the Freedom of the Cuban Five, undated (Box 42)
  - International Committee for Political Prisoners (New York, NY), 1927-1928 (Box 42)
  - International Committee for United Front International Labor Defense, 1945, 1979 (Box 42)
  - International Committee of Conscience on Vietnam (Nyack, NY), undated (Box 42)
  - International Communist Party (Paris, France), undated (Box 42)
  - International Conciliation, 1932 (Box 42)
  - International Confederation for Disarmament and Peace, undated (Box 42)
  - International Conference of Christians and Jews, 1946 (Box 42)
  - International Conference of Youth and Students for Disarmament, Peace and National Independence (Florence, Italy), 1964 (Box 42)
  - International Congress of Women (Hague, Holland), 1915- (Box 42)
  - International Consumerist Party, 1975 (Box 42)
  - International Cooperative Alliance, circa 1954 (Box 42)
  - International Co-ordinating Committee (Paris, France), 1937 (Box 42)
  - International Correspondence (New York, NY), undated (Box 42)
  - International Council Correspondence, undated (Box 42)
  - International Defense and Aid Fund (London, U.K.), 1974-1976 (Box 42)
  - International Defense and Aid Fund for Southern Africa (London, U.K.), 1977-1989 (Box 43)
  - International Federation of Working Women, 1923 (Box 43)
  - International Indian Treaty Council, 1977 (Box 43)
  - International Industrial Relations Association, undated (Box 43)
  - International Institute for Immigrant Girls (New York, NY), undated (Box 43)
  - International Institute for Labor Studies (Switzerland), 1965-1970 (Box 43)
  - International Institute for Research and Education (Amsterdam, Netherlands), circa 1995- (Box 43)
  - International Institute of Social History (Amsterdam, Netherlands), 1968- (Box 43)
  - International Jewish Labor Bund, 1935-1979 (Box 43)
  - International Joint Conference Council of the Commercial and Periodical Branches Printing Industry, 1920 (Box 43)
  - International Juridical Association (New York, NY), 1938-1940 (Box 43)
  - International Labor Defense I, 1925-1944 (Box 43)
  - International Labor Defense II, 1930-1944 (Box 43)
  - International Labor Defense: Eastern New England District, 1938 (Box 43)
  - International Labor Defense: "The International Labor Defense and Black America", 1977 (Box 43)
  - International Labor Defense: Pamphlets and Publications I, 1930-1944 (Box 43)
  - International Labor Defense: Pamphlets and Publications II, 1930-1944 (Box 43)
  - International Labor Defense: Pamphlets and Publications III, 1930-1944 (Box 43)
  - International Labor History Association, 1993- (Box 43)
  - International Labor Organization, 1942 (Box 43)
  - International Labor Press of America, 1922 (Box 43)
  - International Labor Rights Fund, undated (Box 43)
  - International Labour Assistance, Aid for Hungary, undated (Box 43)
  - International League Against War, 1932 (Box 43)
  - International League for the Rights of Man (New York, NY), 1955-1965 (Box 43)
  - International Marxist Group I, 1967-1969 (Box 43)
  - International Marxist Group II, 1967-1969 (Box 43)
  - International Marxist Group: Pamphlets and Publications, 1968-1981, undated (Box 43)
  - International Marxist-Humanist Organization, 2010 (Box 43)
  - International Movement for the Atlantic Union: Membership Directory, 1965 (Box 43)
  - International Network Against State Repression (Chicago, IL), 1985 (Box 43)
  - International Peace Conference on the Pacific and Asian Regions, 1985 (Box 43)
  - International Physicians for the Prevention of Nuclear War, 1984-1985 (Box 43)
  - International Public Service Association, undated (Box 43)
  - International Publishing Company (New York, NY; London, U.K.), 1899, undated (Box 43)
  - International Relief Assocation, undated (Box 43)
  - International Rescue and Relief Committee, undated (Box 43)
  - International Rescue Committee (New York, NY), 1950- (Box 43)
  - International Research Programme Changing Labour Relations in Asia, 1998- (Box 43)
  - International Review (New York, NY), 1938 (Box 43)
  - International Review Service (New York, NY), 1960s (Box 43)
  - International Revolutionary Solidarity Movement, First of May Group, 1976-1980 (Box 43)
  - International School of Social Economy (Chicago, IL), undated (Box 43)
  - International Service for Peace (Santa Cruz, CA), circa 1994 (Box 43)
  - International Socialist Alternative, 1948-1950 (Box 43)
  - International Socialist Brotherhood (Evansville, IN), 1913 (Box 43)
  - International Socialist Club, 1899 (Box 43)
    Materials in this file are related to the campaign for an eight-hour work day.
  - International Socialist Congress, 1896-1914 (Box 43, Box Shared Tamiment 169, Folder 6, Box 125, Folder 26)
  - International Socialist Federation, undated (Box 43)
  - International Socialist Group, undated (Box 44)
  - International Socialist Labour Party: British Section, 1936 (Box 44)
  - International Socialist Organization I, 1970s-1980s (Box 44)
  - International Socialist Organization II, 1970s-1980s (Box 44)
  - International Socialist Organization III, 1970s-1980s (Box 44)
  - International Socialist Organization, 1990s- (Box 44)
  - International Socialist Organization: New York City, 2000- (Box 44)
  - International Socialist Organization: New York North Branch, 1996- (Box 44)
  - International Socialist Organization: New York University Branch, undated (Box 44)
  - International Socialist Organization: Pamphlets and Publications I, 1977-1978 (Box 44)
  - International Socialist Organization: Pamphlets and Publications II, 1977-1978 (Box 44)
  - International Socialist Organization: Pamphlets and Publications, 1980 (Box 44)
  - International Socialist Review, undated (Box 44)
  - International Socialists (Australia), undated (Box 44)
  - International Socialists (Canada), undated (Box 44)
  - International Socialists (Great Britain), 1970s (Box 44)
  - International Socialists (Great Britain): Pamphlets and Publications I, 1970s (Box 44)
  - International Socialists (Great Britain): Pamphlets and Publications II, 1970s (Box 44)
  - International Socialists (U.S.), 1969 (Box 44)
  - International Socialists (U.S.), 1970 (Box 44)
  - International Socialists (U.S.), 1971 (Box 44)
  - International Socialists (U.S.), 1972 (Box 44)
  - International Socialists (U.S.), 1973 (Box 44)
  - International Socialists (U.S.), 1974 (Box 44)
  - International Socialists (U.S.), 1975 (Box 44)
  - International Socialists (U.S.), 1976- (Box 44)
  - International Socialists (U.S.) I, undated (Box 44)
  - International Socialists (U.S.) II, undated (Box 44)
  - International Socialists (U.S.): Convention, 1970-1973 (Box 44)
  - International Socialists (U.S.): Convention, 1976 (Box 44)
  - International Socialists (U.S.): Convention, 1977 (Box 45)
  - International Socialists (U.S.): Convention, 1978 (Box 45)
  - International Socialists (U.S.): Pamphlets and Publications, circa 1970s (Box 45)
  - International Socialists (U.S.): Pamphlets and Publications, 1970-1975 (Box 45)
  - International Socialists (U.S.): Pamphlets and Publications, 1976-1977 (Box 45)
  - International Socialists (U.S.): Pamphlets and Publications, 1980-1981 (Box 45)
  - International Socialists (U.S.): Pamphlets and Publications I, undated (Box 45)
  - International Socialists (U.S.): Pamphlets and Publications II, undated (Box 45)
  - International Society for Labor Law and Social Legislation, undated (Box 45)
  - International Solidarity Committee, 1936-1949 (Box 45)
  - International Solidarity Fund (Paris, France), circa 1938 (Box 45)
  - International Solidarity Movement, 2002- (Box 45)
  - International Song Publishers, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 005, Folder 13)
  - International Student Conference (Nigeria), 1957 (Box 45)
  - International Student - Faculty Strike Day, 1968 (Box 45)
  - International Student Relief (Prague, Czechoslovakia), 1950 (Box 45)
  - International Student Service, 1942-1948 (Box 45)
  - International Symposium on Anarchism (Portland, OR), 1980 (Box 45)
  - International Symposium on Imperialism Its Place in Social Science Today (Elsinore, Denmark), 1971 (Box 45)
  - International Trade Union Committee of Negro Workers, 1929, 1930, undated (Box 45)
  - International Union of Socialist Youth I, 1956-1966 (Box 45)
  - International Union of Socialist Youth II, 1956-1966 (Box 45)
  - International Union of Socialist Youth III, 1956-1966 (Box 45)
  - International Union of Socialist Youth IV, 1956-1966 (Box 45)
  - International Union of Students, 1949-1950 (Box 45)
  - International Union of Students, 1950 (Box 45)
  - International Union of Students, 1951-1960 (Box 45)
  - International Union of Students, 1961-1970 (Box 45)
  - International Union of Students I, 1971-1979 (Box 46)
  - International Union of Students II, 1971-1979 (Box 46)
  - International Union of Students, 1980- (Box 46)
  - International War Crimes Tribunal (Stockholm, Sweden; Roskilde, Denmark), 1967 (Box 46)
  - International Werewolf Conspiracy, undated (Box 46)
  - International Women's Congress Against War and Fascism (Paris, France), 1934 (Box 46)
  - International Women's Day Committee (Great Britain), circa 1949 (Box 46)
  - International Workers' Defense Conference (New York), 1914 (Box 46)
  - International Workers' Defense League of San Francisco (California), 1918 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order, 1930-1932 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order, 1933-1939 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order, 1940-1943 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order, 1944 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order, 1945 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order, 1946-1948 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order, 1950 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order, 1950-1951 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order I, undated (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order II, undated (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order III, undated (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order: Frederick Douglass Fraternal and Benevolent Society, undated (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order: Front Line Fighters Fund, 1942 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order: Polonia Society, 1945 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Party (New York, NY), 1974-1975 (Box 46)
  - International Workingmen's Association, 1872-1933 (Box 46)
  - International Workingmen's Association, 1975-1981 (Box 46)
  - International Working Union of Socialistic Educational Organizations, 1923 (Box 46)
  - International Workmen's Association of America: German Section, 1885 (Box 46)
  - International Youth Alliance (New York, NY), undated (Box 46)
  - International Youth and Students for Social Equality, undated (Box 125, Folder 27)
  - International Youth and Student Movement for the United Nations, 1980 (Box 125, Folder 28)
  - Internationale Gewerkschaftsorganizationen Mahrens Koferenz, 1910 (Box 46)
  - International Ouvriere Socialiste, 1923 (Box 46)
  - Internationales Politisches Antiquariat, undated (Box 46)
  - Internationalism (New York, NY), 1973-1979 (Box 46)
  - Internationalist Group (New York, NY), 1996-2001 (Box 46)
  - Internationalist Perspective (New York, NY), 1970- (Box 46)
  - Internationalist Socialist League (Fourth International), undated (Box 46)
  - Interracial Club (New York, NY), 1942 (Box 46)
  - Interreligious Foundation for Community Organization, Inc. (New York, NY), 1972-1973 (Box 46)
  - Inter-union Institute for Labor and Democracy (New York, NY), 1945 (Box 46)
  - Inter-union Institute on Labor and Defense, 1944 (Box 46)
  - Inter-Varsity Christian Coalition (Box 46)
  - Iranian Students Association of America I, 1976- (Box 46)
  - Iranian Students Association of America II, 1976- (Box 46)
  - Iraqi Communist Party, 1984 (Box 125, Folder 31)
  - Irish-American Labor Coalition, 1985 (Box 46)
  - Irish Communist Organization, 1971 (Box 46)
  - Iron Curtain Refugee Campaign (New York, NY), 1952 (Box 46)
  - Islamic Circle of North America, 2002 (Box 125, Folder 32)
  - Israeleft News Service (Jerusalem, Israel), 1973 (Box 46)
  - Israeli Committee Against House Demolitions, 2011 (Box 46)
  - Italian American Labor Council, Inc. I, 1942- (Box 47)
  - Italian American Labor Council, Inc. II, 1942- (Box 47)
  - Italian American Labor Council, Inc. III, 1942- (Box 47)
  - Italian Emergency Rescue Committee (New York, NY), undated (Box 47)
  - Italian Federation of Labor (Battaglie Sindicali): Serial, 1931 (Box 47)
  - Italian Federation of the Socialist Party (Chicago, IL), undated (Box 47)
  - Italian Socialist Party (Partito Socialista Italiano), undated (Box 47)
  - Izquierda Cristiana (Chile), 1974 (Box 47)
- J, 1911-2008; 5.25 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons, 2 manuscript boxes, and 1 oversize shared box
  - Jabha al-Shabiya li-Tahrir Uman, 1976 (Box 47)
  - Jackrabbit Woman's Press, 1975 (Box 47)
  - Jackson Youth Movement, undated (Box 47)
  - Jamaica Plain/Roxbury Tenant Action Group, 1976 (Box 125, Folder 33)
  - Jamaican Movement for the Advancement of Literacy (JAMAL) I, 1977, undated (Box 47)
  - Jamaican Movement for the Advancement of Literacy (JAMAL) II, 1977, undated (Box 47)
  - James J. Bambrick Jr. and Associates (New York, NY), 1941 (Box 47)
    James J. Bambrick Jr. and Associates was an industrial relations consulting firm.
  - Jane Addams Peace Association (New York, NY), 1961 (Box 47)
  - Jane Addams Peace School (New York, NY), undated (Box 47)
  - Jane Doe Books (Brooklyn, NY), 2000- (Box 47)
  - Japan Council Against A&H Bombs, circa 1960s (Box 47)
  - Japan "Peace for Vietnam!" Committee, 1965 (Box 47)
  - Japanese American Committee for Democracy (New York, NY), circa 1945 (Box 47)
  - Japanese Communist Party, 1989 (Box 125, Folder 34)
  - Japanese Red Army (Nihon Sekigun), 1979 (Box 47)
  - Japanese Youth Fatherland Front, 1951 (Box 47)
  - Jean Field Committee, undated (Box 47)
  - Jeannette Rankin Brigade, undated (Box 47)
  - Jeannette Rankin Rank and File, 1968 (Box 47)
    Materials in this file are related to protests of the Vietnam War.
  - Jefferson Book Shop (New York, NY), undated (Box 47)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science (New York, NY), 1946-1954 (Box 47, Box 125, Folder 35)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science (New York, NY), 1947-1948 (Box 47)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science (New York, NY), 1949 (Box 47)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science (New York, NY), 1951-1952 (Box 47)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science (New York, NY), 1953 (Box 47)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science (New York, NY), 1954-1955 (Box 47)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science (New York, NY) I, undated (Box 47)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science (New York, NY) II, undated (Box 47)
  - Jesus Radicals, 2003 (Box 47)
  - Jeune Socialiste Ouvrier et Paysan, undated (Box 47)
  - Jewish Affairs, 1946-1986 (Box 47)
  - Jewish Americans for World Peace (New York, NY), 1984 (Box 47)
  - Jewish Anarchist Committee, 1986 (Box 47)
  - Jewish Anarchist Community (New York, NY), 1982 (Box 47)
  - Jewish Campaign to End the Indochina Holocaust, undated (Box 47)
  - Jewish Consumptives' Relief Society, 1948 (Box 47)
  - Jewish Currents, 1959-1969 (Box 47)
  - Jewish Currents I, 1970-1979 (Box 47)
  - Jewish Currents II, 1970-1979 (Box 47)
  - Jewish Currents, 1980-1989 (Box 47)
  - Jewish Currents, 1990-1999 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Currents, 2000- (Box 48)
  - Jewish Daily Forward, 1927- (Box 48)
  - Jewish Defense League, undated (Box 48)
  - Jewish Federation-Council of Greater Los Angeles, undated (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Bund, 1955-1961, undated (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee I, 1940-1949, 1995, undated (Box 48, Box 125, Folder 36)
  - Jewish Labor Committee II, 1940-1949 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee III, 1940-1949 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee I, 1950-1959 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee II, 1950-1959 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee III, 1950-1959 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee IV, 1950-1959 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1960-1969 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee I, 1970-1979 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee II, 1970-1979 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee I, 1980-1989 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee II, 1980-1989 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee I, 1990-1993 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee II, 1990-1993 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee I, 1994-1999 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Labor Committee II, 1994-1999 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Labor Committee III, 1994-1999 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Labor Committee I, 2000- (Box 49)
  - Jewish Labor Committee II, 2000- (Box 49)
  - Jewish Labor Committee III, 2000- (Box 49)
  - Jewish Labor Committee IV, 2000- (Box 49)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, undated (Box 49)
  - Jewish Labor Committee: Pamphlets and Brochures, 1940- (Box 49)
  - Jewish Liberation Project (New York, NY), 1969-1971 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Life (New York, NY), 1953, undated (Box 49)
  - Jewish Minorities Research (New York, NY), 1961-1962 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Museum (New York, NY), undated (Box 125, Folder 37)
  - Jewish National Fund, 1958 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Peace Fellowship (New York, NY), undated (Box 49)
  - Jewish Peoples Committee, circa 1930-1942 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Peoples Fraternal Order Cooperative Book League, 1944 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Peoples Fraternal Order of the IWO (U.S.), 1968- (Box 49)
  - Jewish Peoples Fraternal Order of the IWO (U.S.): Jewish Children's Schools of Philadelphia Yearbooks I, 1951-1961 (Box 49)